dirbusiness.co.uk 2017-07-11

# Privacy Notice : dirbusiness.co.uk

This Privacy Policy explains in general terms how we protect the privacy of your personal information . It will apply to any personal information you provide when you register with us.

What information do we collect?

The types of personal information we collect from you will depend on the circumstances of collection and the type of service that you request . For example , when you want to buy a product from this website we may collect details such as your name, email address , shipping address , billing address and other information relevant to your purchase.

As we are required by law to obtain your consent for the collection of "sensitive information " , we will assume that you have consented to the collection of all information provided to us for use in accordance with this policy , unless you tell us otherwise .

How we collect information

We may collect personal information about you when you visit our website, when you deal with us through our website , or when you have contact with us in person . We do not collect any personal information without your consent. We consider that your consent is granted when you complete the fields necessary to facilitate a transaction through this website.

How we use your personal information

Usually, collect your personal information for the following purposes :

1\. To facilitate your access to our website, products and services

2 .To deliver products you have ordered from us

3 .To provide you with information about our products and services

4 .To request your opinion about our products, services , marketing and website .

Disclosure of personal information to third parties

We may disclose your personal information to others for the purpose for which the information was collected or for related purposes , for example to complete a transaction on your behalf or provide you with a product you purchased . We engage third party contractors to perform services for us which involves handling personal information we have the contractor. For example , currently with third party contractors to :

1\. Deliver products purchased from this site

Two . Provide electronic funds transfer , credit card processing and related services account

The security of your personal information

We carried out safely your personal information and we will not trade , rent or sell. We will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information we have about you . Personal information may be stored both electronically on our computer system. Firewalls , passwords , anti-virus software and email filter to protect all our electronic information.

Resolving your concerns

If you have any questions about how your personal information is collected or used , please feel free to contact us . We will respond to your query or complaint as soon as possible .
